http://www.coollawyer.com/privacy-policy.html

Obscenity Definition
About Coollawyer (R)
Obscenity Definition
About Coollawyer (R)
Contact
Privacy Policy
Search by typing & pressing enter
YOUR CART
PRIVACY POLICY (We have text hidden in this form that allows us to determine when you have committed copyright infringement by stealing it and you will receive a cease and desist letter.  If you need a privacy policy, BUY one on this site as part of the Website Forms Set as the below is no substitute.) January 1, 2019 By visiting our site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.  We may change the Privacy Policy from time to time, so check back regularly.  Your continued use indicates your continued acceptance of these terms. Our Commitment to Privacy Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality products and services with integrity in dealing with our users as violation of these rights is anathema to us.  The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.  What Information Do We Collect? When you visit our site you may provide us with two types of information:  personal information you actively choose to disclose (“Active Information”) and use information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our site (“Passive Information”).             No Use of Our Site by Persons Under 13             No person under 13 should disclose information on this site.  You may learn more about protecting children’s privacy online by visiting  www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy. Active Information You Choose to Provide              In order to gain buy a legal form, we may require you to disclose the following information: Your name, email address and phone number for order processing.Your credit card number and information are not collected or retained by our site as they go immediately via secure means for processing your order.   We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer If you choose to post information on our site or maintain email, snailmail or telephone contact with us, we may retain such information also and its transmission via email is not secured.             Passive Information Collected              What is a Cookie?               Cookies are a feature of web browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, etc.) software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site.  They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transaction on related web pages.  This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet.  Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.            Our site utilizes cookies to collect information about how our site is used.  Passive Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at our site, the sites visited just before, just after our site, enable the site to recognize you, for example by:  remembering your user ID, offering an online shopping cart,  keeping track of your preferences if you visit the website again.  If you do not wish to transmit “cookie” information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the “Help” section of your browser to correctly do so.  You can also learn about tracker blockers: there are tools that allow you to block ads called tracker blockers. To find tracker blocking plug-ins, type “tracker blocker” in your search engine. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturerHowever, please keep in mind that if you turn off the use of Cookies, some features of the site that you enjoy may not be available to you.  For example, what you last viewed or saving items in your shopping cart.  If you wish to re-enable such features, please re-enable Cookies.                 You may OPT OUT of cookies by indicating such on the banner to this site.Other Passive Information That May Be Collected.Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our website, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our  number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes.                                   How Do We Use the Information Collected? Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction, use Active Information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer services such as support, and making available other products or services we think may be of interest to our users.  We may use the Active Information or Passive Information you provide to us to contact you about changes to our site, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you shall find valuable.  If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, you may “opt-out” of doing so by sending an email to us. We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance and design our site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use.  Additionally, cookies help us know information about how many people visit our site, when they visit and how they use our service.  Passive Information may result in your viewing of particular advertising based on your user habits for your viewing on our site and a shopping experience customized to you in content, services and goods.  Your Information in Relationship to Others We Link ToYou may be able to access other websites through our site.  When you do so you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those sites’ privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. When you choose to shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases. Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third PartiesWe may disclose anonymous information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics to advertisers on our site.  The parties who perform services for us such as Weebly and SquareUp may also have access to your information in performing such services.  Should we buy or sell assets of our company, another company may need to review our company’s assets, including your information, to make business decisions as to whether to acquire such assets. Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law  We may be required by subpoena, law, investigation, notification due to data breach or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive Information you have provided to us.  Sharing Information in Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets.  Also, in the unlikely event that our business or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. How Do We Secure Active Information and Passive Information?  We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Active Information and Passive Information.  Your postings on this site and other communications you may have with us via email or snailmail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information.  Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means. How Can You Choose Not to Receive Information About Products or Services By Us or to Correct, Delete or Access Your Information If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you or if you wish to access, delete or correct you information, please send us an email to us.                                             . California Residents If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name registration, the site name you visited and a return address or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Requests made via email will not be accepted. Please mail your request to Coollawyer LLC, 700 Blanding Blvd, STE 13-313, Orange Park, FL 32065.
LEGAL ARTICLES ARE NOT A SUBSTITUTE FOR AN ATTORNEY AND ARE NOT LEGAL ADVICE.  ALWAYS CONSULT AN ATTORNEY BEFORE USE OF LEGAL FORMSAS THE LAW CHANGES WITH TIME AND JURISDICTION.  Judith Silver, author of the articles and information on this site, is located in  FL, and is an attorney licensed in FL, CA, NY and TX .(c) 2000-2020 Coollawyer LLCPrivacy Policy     /    Contact Us
